[Theme song]
[Exciting music plays]
[People cheering]
[Italian]
Have a good night, lady.
[Korean]
Look at me for a second.
Follow me
[People cheering]
[laughter]
Hey there!
[Exciting music plays]
[Car door slams shut]
(Sunam)
Stop, stop, stop
wait
IC
Hey, let's go first.
[Sunam’s sigh]
(Load 1)
What is it?
(Sunam)
(bodyguard)
You must check your temperature to enter.
[Sunam and his subordinates laugh]
[Sunam’s annoying groan]
[Thermometer operating sound]
- Come in.
- (Sunam) Ah, Mr.
Why is Police Officer Kim here?
(police)
Huh?
(Sunam)
Even though I know I shouldn’t be here today
Hey, did you come because you wanted to come?
I came here for security reasons.
- Security?
- (Police) Oh
What security?
[sigh]
[People talk in English]
(Italian Ambassador)
[English]
Oh my god!
[Laugh together]
Nice to meet you, let’s cheers.
[People keep talking in English]
[Korean]
IC
[Interesting music]
[Subordinate 2’s angry groan]
Ana, me, Mr.
[People are noisy]
[Chayoung takes a breath]
[Vincenzo laughs slightly]
[Chayoung laughs]
at one's own expense
Even throwing a big party like this
(Chayoung)
Prevent forced demolition
This is neither good nor malicious.
What's the real reason?
Why on earth? Why?
bralo suit
And it’s different every day
A person who changes clothes
Why is it so bad that it's like this here?
Do you know Bralo?
[Chayoung laughs]
[grabs Vincenzo]
(Chayoung)
Is there anyone who doesn't know Bralo?
Bralo, the artisan of Milan’s handmade suits!
[Elasticity]
What is the real purpose of doing this?
[Vincenzo takes a breath]
I fell in love with this place
[Soft music]
(Chayoung)
Why?
Is there a reason to love?
(Chayoung)
There must be
Everyone pretends there is no reason
There's a reason for everything
I like love without reason better
What is it?
From this mystery to romance
What about the unexpected transition?
(Italian Ambassador)
[Italian]
my friend Vincenzo
Come here!
(Vincenzo)
Yes, Ambassador, I will be right there.
(Italian Ambassador)
What a party!
[laughter]
Take a break
[Chayoung’s surprised moan]
[Korean]
Oh my, why are you whispering all of a sudden?
(Yeonjin)
Oh my, oh my, oh my!
Oh my gosh, party with us.
[Cheolwook hums]
[Cheolwook speaks]
(Yeonjin)
It's free, but they're just trying to make a living.
Oh my, look at this fear
- (Yeonjin) Say ho!
- (Larry Kang) Ho!
[Yeonjin’s laughter]
(Cheolwook)
♪ The ghost that ate and died has beautiful stains ♪
[Yeonjin cheers]
[Cheolwook continues humming]
[cell phone vibrating sound]
[Seokdo sharpens his toenails]
[Seokdo grabs his cell phone]
(Seokdo)
uh
[Interesting music]
What?
This, Italian university, ambassador?
Oh, why is she there?
Hey, just push it all in.
Fold it
[Humorous sound effects]
(Seunghyuk)
[screaming]
No, black tea, you really!
Oh, I'm going crazy, really, Mr.
Even without reporting such a serious matter,
[Pouring a drink]
Do you have any thoughts or not, huh?
What are we going to do with this?
[Myunghee’s sigh]
(Myunghee)
The researcher
[Seunghyuk sighs]
If you notify the media or the victim,
What are you going to do?
(Seunghyuk)
Yes!
For the time being, researchers
You won't be able to move easily
- (Seunghyuk) Huh?
- On what basis do you make that conclusion?
yes
I have been a lawyer for 8 years now.
I am more confident than anyone else.
[Myunghee snorts]
(Seunghyuk)
Persimmon?
[Interesting music]
(Myunghee)
Hey, in front of a prosecutor with 20 years of experience.
Persimmons and all, well, so
I don't think this is something to brag about, right?
yes!
(Chayoung)
The prosecutor's time is 20 years.
Isn’t this your first time working as a lawyer?
- (Myunghee) Huh?
- I'll say it again.
I didn't give it to you because I was afraid.
(Chayoung)
I'm confident I can solve it and I don't want to worry
I didn't report it.
(Myunghee)
Hey
Think of your superiors, come on
The bowl is big, our 8th year Hong Byeon
Huh?
- (Chayoung) CEO!
- (Seunghyuk) He’s like this again.
(Chayoung)
Attorney Choi
If you believe me
Give trust instead of blame
Ugh, I'm scared, really, at times like this.
(Myunghee)
Give it to me, trust me
Instead, when something happens, trust is lost and
[makes a loud noise]
Give it up, okay?
Thank you for your generous generosity.
[Humorous sound effects]
(Chayoung)
Don't even think about going home today
Yoo Min-cheol's family, relatives, classmates, co-workers
Pull out a list of everything
Oh, and
Invoice the administrative team in the morning
- with cache
- (Junwoo) Okay
[surprised moan]
(Junwoo)
No, are you going to get this big money and spend it?
Looking for acquaintances
To the person who gives me a clue to the whereabouts
To shoot right away
It's not some kind of 'Car Quiz on the Block'
Why do you go around and give me money?
What money can solve
It's best to solve it with money
(Chayoung)
No one gets hurt
This is the method with the highest satisfaction.
[Elasticity]
[elegant music]
[English]
It's amazing
It's really the best
[People cheering]
(Cheolwook)
[Korean]
Finally went!
[Noisy]
(Yoochan)
I'm going first
- (Cheolwook) Together, together, together
- (Yoochan) No, no.
[Yoo-chan and Cheol-wook’s laughter]
- (Yeonjin) Oh, why, why don’t you do it together?
- (Cheolwook) Come in!
[People are noisy]
- (Yeonjin) Plaza!
- (Hee-su) Plaza!
[Cheolwook’s spirit]
[People laughing]
(Cheolwook)
Come on, everyone!
[Each person speaks]
- (Toto) Gold price
- (Cheolwook) Plaza!
(Larry Kang)
Plaza!
- (Heesu) We are tenants!
- (Yeonjin) Oh, it’s a tenant.
(Heesu)
surely
(Tenant)
Win!
- (Cheolwook) Eurachacha!
- (Toto) Gold price, gold price, fighting!
(Tenant)
Fighting!
[People cheering]
[Cheolwook whistles]
(Hongsik)
Oh, it's nice to be warm.
(Heesu)
Yeah, this was yesterday.
It’s not bad, eat it.
(Toto)
[Laughing]
I understand
[Yeonjin’s elasticity]
- (Toto) The tteokbokki here is...
- (Cheolwook) Hey
[Heesu’s laughter]
(Cheolwook)
Party, this costs 10 million won
I think it's broken
(Yeonjin)
No, about two or three thousand is enough, huh?
Moreover, Attorney Vincenzo
You did it all with your own money.
Hey
[Interesting music]
What happened until yesterday
They said ‘dog bird’ and ‘cow bird’
‘Lawyer’ today?
[People laughing]
(Yeonjin)
Wow, bitch, really.
(Heesu)
I was a little skeptical at first
If you see me doing this,
It seems like he's sincere, huh?
(in advance)
If you are a really strange person
Would you spend your own money to do this?
(Heesu)
That's right
(Hongsik)
Did you say the party will continue if we have to?
[People laughing]
It won't be long before things break, huh?
- (Cheolwook) No
- (Yeonjin) Yes
(Cheolwook)
I don't believe it 100% either.
[Yeonjin responds]
Well, for now, I'm going to take our side.
[People respond]
(Toto)
These days, me and Attorney Vincenzo
We communicate in Italian style.
[Toto’s laughter]
[Cheolwook’s elasticity]
Attorney Vincenzo's report
It seemed like he was just hiding?
[Toto’s awkward laughter]
It's not hiding, it's a kind of play.
Yes, in Italy, people communicate with each other.
I'm basically hiding
[Heesu’s laughter]
italian mafia games
[Toto’s awkward laughter]
[Cheolwook’s laughter]
[moktak sound effect]
(Chae Shin)
continue for us
If you take the lead like today
Truly sent by Buddha
Maybe it's a person
- Avalokitesvara Bodhisattva
- (Toto) Amen
- (Toto) Oh my gosh
- (Hongsik) What is Amen? Amen.
[Toto’s awkward laughter]
(in advance)
I'm only talking about it now
He, the Italian lawyer.
Aren’t you so handsome?
[Interesting music]
You have great skin too
The perfume smells so good too
Right, right?
Director Seo felt that too, right?
- Yes
- (Yeonjin) It was good.
(Heesu)
Well, let’s talk about it out loud.
Well, Hou Dae is in very good condition, right?
The boss
Well, you don’t like that style.
What kind of girl doesn't like that style?
[Vincenzo’s powerful moans]
[Vincenzo’s sigh]
[sigh]
[Exciting music]
(Vincenzo)
A party alone cannot stop demolition.
I need something more certain
(Chayoung)
researchers control
Please make me stronger, team leader.
Yes, definitely not going out for even an hour.
Yes, please, team leader.
[Exciting music plays]
(people)
Awesome
[People laughing]
(Chayoung)
Oh my, what is it?
- (Yun Byeon) Oh, good morning.
- (Park Byun) Are you here?
(Yun Byeon)
Come quickly
[Chayoung says hello]
(Attorney 1)
What, what are you doing now?
- (Yun Byeon) Look, look.
- (Chayoung) Oh my
(Myunghee)
Ha, hoo!
Huh, huh, huh, it's killing me!
Huh, huh, huh!
[People's elasticity]
(Yun Byeon)
We no, no, no, oh no
(Park Byun)
Isn't this it? huh?
What is this?
[Myunghee’s heavy breathing]
(Myunghee)
It's killing me
[Myunghee’s heavy breathing]
Hey
- (Chayoung) It’s amazing.
- (Myunghee) That’s right.
This is why you became an ace
[Chayoung sighs]
(Junwoo)
Isn’t the bracelet pretty?
Can you see the bracelet too?
Isn’t this a new product from Blamino?
[Chayoung sighs]
The hottest thing these days
(Chayoung)
I know everything
[Junwoo’s strange groan]
[Chayoung’s disapproving groan]
[Junwoo clears his throat]
(Junwoo)
Because I know everything
Please finish the internship quickly.
Let me be your senior partner
(Chayoung)
Why me?
(Junwoo)
Oh, um, we work together.
I also go to watch baseball
I went to eat chicken and beer and it was so good.
Isn't that work and not love?
[bright music]
Then it's better
Work hard and rely on each other
[English]
dreams come true
[Korean]
I'm tired and childish
I don't do any in-office dating.
Give up your dreams!
Okay
What did I order earlier?
(Junwoo)
Ah, that's right
[Junwoo clears his throat]
I got it from the Italian Bar Union.
You're a lawyer, right?
(Chayoung)
Tsk
What is your criminal record?
(Junwoo)
It's clean
[Chayoung sighs]
But he’s very handsome, isn’t he?
[bright music]
- Are you doing that because you have other interests?
- (Chayoung) Any other interests?
Right? Right?
The man you fell in love with at first sight?
That's why you said you didn't like me
(Chayoung)
Hey, hey!
[Humorous sound effects]
You're just saying it's someone else's life
[laughter]
(Vincenzo)
What is it?
What is the angle of that chin?
(Toto)
Jigayu, so far
I thought I wasn't good at cooking
That's not it
Did you see it yesterday?
everyone who came to the party
My Margherita Pizza
Did you see him eating it deliciously or not?
huh?
[Interesting music]
The Italian Ambassador
Well, you must have lived in Italy for a year or two?
My wife and I came and tasted it and gave it a thumbs up.
So it's not over?
(Vincenzo)
When people get drunk
That, in Korean expression
uh
I can't tell if it tastes like poop or soybean paste.
(Toto)
No, it's delicious.
[humorous music]
Why, why do you keep insisting to yourself?
They say it's all delicious
Then make one exactly the same.
yes, draw
Just wait here
[Tense sound effect]
(Toto)
Mr. Lee
[Toto’s heavy breathing]
(Toto)
Taste it
Tsk
[Interesting music]
Well, I'm confident.
It’s so delicious, you’ll go crazy, right?
[Tense sound effect]
[Embarrassed groan]
[Vincenzo gags]
No…
[tragic music]
What else, yes?
No, why?
[Vincenzo laughs]
[Vincenzo takes a breath]
This, basil and cheese
Are you practicing social distancing?
We are playing completely separately.
[Interesting music]
[Vincenzo’s laughter]
(Vincenzo)
Oh, and the tomatoes are in self-quarantine?
There is no flavor at all.
[Toto is crying]
Yeah
[Vincenzo puts down the money]
I had a good time
This pizza-shaped trash, huh?
[Crying]
[Toto’s angry groan]
(Kiseok)
Wow, it’s Vincenzo.
- Do you know me?
- (Kiseok) Ah, uh…
[Interesting music]
yesterday party
Oh, a party?
Did you first see me at the party?
No, yes!
It was my first time seeing you
Is this really your first time?
[The door clicks open]
(Joosung)
Lawyer!
Attorney Hong came to work.
(Vincenzo)
yes, i understand
[Slight moan]
[Interesting music]
[Kiseok clears his throat]
[breathes and then exhales]
[Kiseok’s nervous breathing]
[Sniffles]
But
What perfume do you use?
[Sniffles]
[Kiseok’s elasticity]
[Interesting music]
(Kiseok)
hello
(Toto)
Welcome
(Kiseok)
Oh yeah, I'm not a guest
I ate the chef's pizza at the party yesterday.
I was moved indescribably
So Italian pasta
I came because I wanted to learn
Right?
It was really delicious, right?
yes
(Toto)
Mr. Lee
But it's like our kitchen assistant.
I'm not looking for it
just go for it
All you have to do is put him to sleep in a corner.
Well, salary, meals.
You don't have to take it.
(Kiseok)
yo, cooking assistant, cleaning, serving, chores
I will do everything
Master
[Bell sound effect]
(Toto)
Huh? Su, teacher…
(Kiseok)
Yesterday, I ate teacher’s pizza.
As soon as I take a bite
The bells of Florence's Duomo Cathedral
It rang in my ears
[elegant music]
When I took two bites
The sound of the ship's horn in the port of Naples, yes
It resonated throughout my body.
[Imitates the sound of a boat horn]
(Toto)
Oh, oh Naples
[Toto’s Elasticity]
(Kiseok)
Ah, yes, I…
With the teachings of Master
I want to create Italy
Ah, but is it really a salary?
Even if we don’t provide meals or anything like that…
Yes, all you need is a space to sleep.
And before
All you need is Master
[Bell sound effect]
[elegant music]
[in a low voice]
What is your name?
(Vincenzo)
Babel Pharmaceutical’s new drug
Do you know what the main ingredient of RDU-90 is?
(Yoochan)
Ah, yes
Uh, it's a substance called Koisanic.
That Koisanik
The fact that it is a narcotic ingredient
Did you know?
Narcotic?
[Meaningful music]
Uh, this is my first time hearing this.
(Joosung)
Uh, according to our advice
It's a general painkiller ingredient.
[laughter]
Babel Pharmaceuticals systematically
You deceived the lawyer.
[Sighing]
I don't even know that
If this drug is released
The spread of drugs
Isn't it the same thing?
(Vincenzo)
That's right
Official painkiller addict
It will increase
But what's more dangerous is
Because of narcotic painkillers like in the US
a real drug addict
It may increase
(Joosung)
Then
[Jusung clears his cough]
Because of this drug, Korea
Is there a possibility of mass distribution of drugs?
(Vincenzo)
Maybe like America, South America, Italy
There might be a big drug cartel.
(Yoochan)
Not yet
The spread of drugs in this small country
It will be an instant
I don't even want to imagine it
like in a movie
Even young students can easily
You can get drugs
Near home and school
[Joosung sighs]
(Yoochan)
Ha, indeed
no, how
Can you make a medicine like this?
Because I don’t mind going to jail
I really want to burn it all down, just
Just eat it all, leaving nothing behind!
We need to stop this
Whatever it takes
We have to stop this
[sigh]
[cell phone vibrating sound]
yes
[Meaningful music]
Yes, I'll be down soon.
[Meaningful sound effects]
(worker)
During construction, the Buddha statue...
(Vincenzo)
There is no need to build a boiler, monk.
(Chae Shin)
No, what is this all about?
[moktak sound effect]
[Chae-shin’s painful moans]
(Chae Shin)
No, lawyer, you can't do this.
[Interesting music]
No, without our permission...
Boiler construction cost
Please help me survive.
(Vincenzo)
Please take a moment
(Chae Shin)
No…
(Vincenzo)
And the monthly electricity bill is
I will bear the burden, monk.
(Chae Shin)
Oh no, no.
That can't be happening.
(Vincenzo)
[Strengthening]
That one, yeah
(Chae Shin)
This way?
(Vincenzo)
Ah, I can put it here.
(Chae Shin)
Uh, huh?
(Vincenzo)
Ah…
(Chae Shin)
Huh?
[Vincenzo’s embarrassed groan]
(Vincenzo)
Hey, monk, take a moment to touch your right hip...
[Elasticity of dropping]
[moktak sound effect]
[Vincenzo’s powerful moans]
Yes, you are welcome, monk.
thank you
What are you doing, that, that?
(Chae Shin)
What is that?
(Vincenzo)
Put it here, put it here
[Fast forward sound effect]
(Kiseok)
Catholic mafia for monks
Electric mats are being laid in the temple.
What on earth is going on?
[Vincenzo speaks]
Is it a great unification of religions?
Merciful, this man.
(Student 1)
Just give me one
(Student 2)
one car
[Student 3 laughs]
- (Student 2) Ah…
- (Student 1) Take it out quickly, if you have it.
[Youngho’s laughter]
(Student 1)
Oh, what do you do when you’re not always there?
(Youngho)
Hey, give me one too.
(Student 2)
Ah…
- (Student 3) Hey, I have two.
- (Student 2) Just smoke one.
(Youngho)
Oh, please be quiet.
[Game sound plays]
Oh, give me a lighter, please.
(Student 1)
Don't you have a lighter?
- (Student 2) Yes
- (Student 3) No way
(Student 1)
give it to me quickly
[Student 2 laughs]
Hey, give me a light, quickly.
mom don't smoke
Didn't you?
(Youngho)
Hey, I'm embarrassed to talk about my mom
Oh, hurry up
Have you guys never heard of that?
If you smoke from a young age...
(Youngho)
Are you saying your bones are drying out?
It was so ripe that it was ripe.
(Student 1)
uncle
Let’s give some money before we go.
[Student 3’s surprised gasp]
(Student 3)
Hey, my uncle
Does the watch look good too?
[Student 1’s elasticity]
Now
If you promise not to smoke with me,
I can give you at least some pocket money.
(Youngho)
Man, don’t you know that middle schoolers are scary?
If we're mad, we don't care about people.
Now, all the cigarettes you have
[Tapping the trash can with his foot]
Let's throw it in the trash can here.
(Student 1)
Uncle, in the world
What is the scariest bread?
[Vincenzo’s thinking groan]
[Exciting music]
If the answer is straight bread, I'm disappointed.
[Student 1 laughs]
(Student 1)
It's the correct answer
[Student 1 groans in pain]
It hurts, wait…
[Student 3’s spirit]
[Students moan in pain]
[Vincenzo’s sigh]
[Student 1 groans with difficulty]
(Vincenzo)
[Italian]
These bad guys
Troublesome people!
[Students moan in pain]
(Vincenzo)
[Korean]
Come to work
[Moaning in pain]
[Youngho moans in pain]
- (Vincenzo) Throw it away
- IC
[Moaning in pain]
(Youngho)
Ai, ah, I'll throw it away, I'll throw it away
[Youngho moans in pain]
Get tested every time you see me from now on
(Vincenzo)
Got it?
Hey, what is it?
[Meaningful music]
(Kiseok)
The mafia is leading the youth.
I've lived a dark path
Is it a reflection on yourself?
The more I know about this man, the less I understand him.
[Vincenzo’s sigh]
(Vincenzo)
For the first and last time
This is advice
[laughter]
[Investment and Development Team Leader Sighs]
(Investment Development Team Leader)
But
I don't know about threats
I don't think you're in a position to listen to advice.
[Exciting music]
[Investment and Development Team Leader’s angry groan]
Forward!
Who will be praying to whom?
We'll see
Sounds fun.
(Joosung)
Hey!
Mr. my bike
(Vincenzo)
boss
Team leader, please scan me.
(Vincenzo)
Who will pray first
You'll find out
[Chayoung sobs]
[sad music]
(Chayoung)
My youngest brother also graduated from pharmacy school.
Working hard in the lab every night
I come home tired
[Sobbing]
Thinking about career path
[Man 1 sighs]
[Chayoung continues to sob]
(Junwoo)
senior
no
leave me like this
(Junwoo)
senior
thank you
[Sobbing]
[Chayoung sighs]
[Interesting music]
[Mouse click sound]
That’s why Mincheol doesn’t look like anyone else.
(Chayoung)
It must already be hard these days
If you happen to be alone
I'm worried that people might think it's strange...
It's been a few months since I talked to Mincheol on the phone.
Don't do that.
If you have ever been contacted
(Chayoung)
please tell me
Examples of information provided
I'll do enough
I have a lot of money?
[Humorous sound effects]
[humorous music]
The amount is larger than expected
[Junwoo clears his throat]
(Junwoo)
no
This is really for Mincheol.
If you have ever been in contact...
(Man 1)
If you don't go
[Man 1 clears his throat]
I will report it to the police
You're reporting it, let's go.
[The door clicks open]
[Junwoo clears his throat]
[Junwoo rustles the ice cream]
[Junwoo’s encouraging groan]
(Chayoung)
How can you see my tears
There may be no reaction, right?
Ah, I cried and it got hotter
(Junwoo)
No matter how much I think about it
If I were Yoo Min-cheol
The only place I can go is my senior father.
I don't think there will be
straw
Try to persuade your father well.
You're my daughter
Be honest with each other, okay?
If that had worked, I would have done it already.
[Junwoo sighs]
(Junwoo)
If you expose Whistleblower
Senior, I'm in real trouble.
(Chayoung)
Hey
You're from New Yorker
Why are you so crazy?
Why worry about other people so much?
(Junwoo)
No…
I'm only worried about my senior.
[Interesting music]
Acting assistant without me
I'm worried about who will match me
I'm worried about how I'll find my car in the parking lot without me
(Chayoung)
By the way, where did you put it today?
[Junwoo sighs]
- (Junwoo) Exit B on the first basement floor
- (Chayoung) Uh
(Junwoo)
senior
Isn’t idol work too much of a headache?
Do you want to jump somewhere else?
my old man in boston
I am planning to open a law firm in Korea soon.
A new law firm cannot cover my salary.
[Junwoo sighs]
[cell phone vibrating sound]
Uh, Seo-byeon
(Seopyeon)
Attorney Choi Myung-hee said this evening,
A company meeting was called.
(Seopyeon)
Only 5 years or more
They say I can’t go because of work.
(Seopyeon)
No, no one else knows
I must bring you, senior.
uh
Baby, you care about me more than you really need to
(Yoochan)
It's not hard at all
I'm back again
A skilled lawyer, yes.
I'm so happy
please trust me
You say I can win?
[sigh]
[Meaningful music]
[breathes and then exhales]
(Yoochan)
How did you make this difficult decision?
(Mincheol)
I felt it while watching the trial.
If I remain silent, people who feel wronged
It's getting too much
Okay, well thought out.
(Yoochan)
thank you so much
Uh, well then, the facts that are currently revealed and
What is the most different?
The new drug development team's new drug experiment is
It was no different from intentional murder.
Yes?
instructed above
RDU-90, a painkiller being prepared for release
(Mincheol)
Give unlimited doses to five people
Let's experiment to see how much people can endure.
No, how could you give such an order...
And RDU-90 is not a general painkiller.
[ECG meter beeping sound]
(Mincheol)
It is a narcotic painkiller.
[Chuckling]
[ECG alarm sound]
[Subject's painful moans]
[nervous music]
[Painful groan]
[Subject's painful moans]
(Mincheol)
Babel Pharmaceuticals does not care about the lives of test subjects.
I didn't care from the beginning
I tried to quit the experiment, but
I received threats to harm my family.
All facts in court
Could you testify?
The safety of me and my family
You guarantee it, right?
[Embarrassed groan]
It's hard right now, but I can do it somehow
Let's create the conditions
(Mincheol)
What do you mean by that?
Without that too
What do I believe and testify about?
and
The lawyer said he wouldn't reveal me.
There is no guarantee, right?
Ah, no, Mr. Mincheol.
Uh, only I know what happened today.
I will take all the risk alone.
Please believe me
(Mincheol)
No
If safety is not guaranteed
I think it would be difficult to speak in vain.
sorry
(Yoochan)
Attorney Vincenzo
What kind of medicine is that?
i already knew
I'm going to take it all on my own
I pretended not to notice
I somehow
I will definitely stop it with my own hands.
[sigh]
(Vincenzo)
Lawyer
Ah, lawyer.
(Yoochan)
Ah, cigarettes…
Don't burn it, really.
[Yuchan’s laughter]
the essence of this incident
Are you getting it right?
The essence?
(Vincenzo)
Pharmaceutical company plans to launch narcotic painkiller
Invisible political lobbyist
Huge kickbacks, trial manipulation
This itself is the Korean Cartel.
I know that much.
If you know so well
Shouldn’t we just let go?
[Meaningful music]
(Vincenzo)
These people are not businessmen
It's a monster
I don't care about people's lives.
If you keep holding on
I'll win someday, right?
The lawyer
You can never defeat a monster
A person can defeat a monster
no
That's only possible in mythology
Only negative words today
Are you choosing?
The lawyer is now
You're standing at a dead end.
There's no way
I somehow
I'm going to break down that alley wall.
Even if my fist breaks
[sigh]
Tsk
When you come across a dead end
Getting out of there
It's the wisest thing to do
[cell phone vibrating sound]
Hello
yes
Ah, when…
[sigh]
Which hospital?
yes
Yes, I will go right away, yes
[Vincenzo’s sigh]
Come with me.
Where?
(Yoochan)
Let's go first
[A siren rings in the distance]
(Yoochan)
Oh no, take it easy
Why does a sick man go to work?
Ugh, try becoming a public defender.
I'm dying from this, really.
I…
Ah, there it is
Come on, let's go.
Come on, let's go in.
I'll wait outside
Let’s meet up and come out.
[Yoo-chan grabs Vincenzo]
Let's watch it together while we're here.
I'll give you a favor too, okay?
Oh, I…
[sigh]
(Yoochan)
Ah, yes, thank you for your hard work.
[Correction staff responds]
I'm a lawyer
yes
[Calm music]
Am I right?
It was a good idea to come close to a big hospital, right?
yes
[Gyeongja laughs]
(Yoochan)
Ha, am I really laughing?
I almost paid the invoice.
(Gyeongja)
just
Let's say I practiced dying once, okay?
But who?
(Yoochan)
Ah…
Ah, uh, here
Uh…
Helping me with that job this time
I'm a lawyer, yes.
He’s handsome, right?
(Gyeongja)
yes
You're really handsome
I have something to talk about.
Let's talk
(Yoochan)
I'm going to apply for a retrial.
(Gyeongja)
Without my permission anyway
Because I can't do anything
Do whatever you want
(Yoochan)
If you really go out like this,
Only those who did bad things
It makes the world easier to live in.
'Cause it's been a long time since I stopped caring about things like that
Don't make work
[Gyeongja’s labored breathing]
[sigh]
[cell phone vibrating sound]
yes
(Investment Development Team Leader)
I am the investment and development team leader at Babel Construction.
Did you leave a text message in the morning?
[Rhythmic music plays]
[People cheering]
(Myunghee)
It's a one shot
(people)
thank you
(Myunghee)
Listen all the way, all the way, comfortably
(people)
thank you
[Lawyer 2 speaks]
[The glasses are rattling]
[Refreshing moan]
(Myunghee)
Now, uh
Today, huh?
He's a lawyer, damn it.
Let's play childishly for once
[People applauding and cheering]
[People’s encouraging groans]
(Park Byun)
What do you want?
our lawyer
Who, what, personal skills, etc.
Is there anyone who can do it? Personal skill
(Yun Byeon)
His personal skills are the best here.
The vocal imitation is amazing.
Let's see, give it a try
- (Seobyeon) Yes
- (Yun Byeon) Show me
[Seobyeon’s powerful moans]
(people)
Show me, show me!
[Imitating Yoo Hae-jin]
Write, ah, this is Go Gwang-ryeol.
[Interesting music]
[People laughing]
(Seopyeon)
Ah, I came here at the request of a swan.
Ah, the swan is now
Instead of being busy with work,
Oh, he wants me to give him some money.
[Seobyun’s laughter]
Ah, that export
I work for a small company.
Ah, the tingling…
Battery
[Seobyun’s laughter]
[People laughing]
- (Myunghee) You’re good, uh, you’re good.
- You're good at it.
- Anglerfish
- (Myunghee) Oh, what?
[Imitating Kim Yun-seok]
Stop moving, take off the hem?
[Myunghee’s elasticity]
My defeat and Madam Jeong’s defeat
Did you take it out from underneath?
Do I look like I'm wearing hot pants?
(Seunghyuk)
Yerim, look at that card!
Don't touch the paddle
The hairs are flying away
Bring a hammer
[Myunghee’s laughter]
[Imitating Jo Sang-geon]
I did this stupid thing
[Seunghyuk’s laughter]
(Myunghee)
Now
Oh, now, now, go over there.
[Seunghyuk’s drunken moaning]
Well done, well done, applause
[People applauding and cheering]
Who's next? Is there anyone?
(Myunghee)
Is this it?
Then our idol’s ace
Let's go to Hongbyeon
[Exciting music]
red stool
(Park Byun)
Chayoung Hong
(people)
Hong Cha-young, Hong Cha-young!
I don't do that.
Where can I find something like that, hurry up
I don't like doing this at a drinking party.
(Myunghee)
Because I'm so special
I'm not asking you to do this.
You've committed a big sin, huh?
Doing things like this will give you a small score.
I'm telling you to make up for it.
[sigh]
Tsk
(Chayoung)
Then, I will also do a vocal imitation.
Hey, good, applause!
[People's exclamation and applause]
[Music that heightens the mood]
[deep breath]
[Exciting music]
(Chayoung)
Huh, huh, huh, kill me!
Huh, huh!
Huh, huh, huh, huh
Huh, huh, huh
It's killing me!
Huh, huh, huh, it's killing me!
Huh, huh, huh
[laughter]
Huh, it's killing me!
Huh, huh, huh, it's killing me!
[laughter]
(Chayoung)
Wow, it's killing me
Huh, it's killing me!
[Myunghee’s laughter]
Huh, it's killing me! her!
[People laughing]
[Atmospheric music plays]
[Investment and Development Team Leader laughs]
Are you drinking coffee?
(Investment Development Team Leader)
No, what happened?
Do you want a busy person to come and go?
(Vincenzo)
From now on, I direct
I only do two things
[laughter]
Are you giving me orders all of a sudden?
(Vincenzo)
first
for the next two months
Preventing Geumga Plaza from being demolished
second
When the plaza is demolished
Having a company I know demolish it
[laughter]
What are you…
Did you turn?
What kind of bullshit are you talking about, tsk
[Vincenzo opens the bag]
[Investment and Development Team Leader laughs]
I'm curious
[Interesting music]
(Vincenzo)
Didn't I tell you last time?
I won't stay still anymore
You took bribes without the company knowing
list of real estate agents
Park Seok-do, the gangster who took your orders
Record of threatening businessmen
[Embarrassed groan]
(Investment Development Team Leader)
Ha, oh
[surprised moan]
[Rhythmic music]
Ah…
[shaking breathing]
(Vincenzo)
The affair partner, Manager Kim Moran of Management Team 2,
[Investment and Development Team Leader’s surprised gasp]
Your Shaina Hotel check-in photo
It was broad daylight, and…
(Investment Development Team Leader)
Ah, there
[Awkward laughter]
Please stop it.
Tsk, well, this is enough
To be socially buried
I think it's enough
yes, that's enough
(Investment Development Team Leader)
So I'm asking you a favor.
Really, these facts
I really can't
(Vincenzo)
If you just follow my instructions from now on
All records will be deleted
sweet
Manager Kim Moran of Management Team 2 quickly organized the
go back to home
a married person
Well, but
How can I last two months?
Postponing demolition?
(Investment Development Team Leader)
Even a month is hard, and
Ugh, I don't have much strength.
I, I, I am a salaried worker.
That's none of my business
(Vincenzo)
Do it no matter what
If you fail
I lived my whole life being pointed at.
Because I will let you die
[Painful groan]
[Investment and Development Team Leader Sighs]
Oh, and a warning
(Vincenzo)
Don't do anything nonsense
If I'm wrong you die
[Interesting music]
Ah, ah, sir, sir.
(Investment Development Team Leader)
Ah, ah, we're in big trouble.
Ah, what, ah, what should I do?
Ah, you're in big trouble, ah
(Seunghyuk)
Should I have another drink?
- (Park Byun) Representative, please come in.
- (Seobyeon) Yes, please come in.
(Seunghyuk)
Where and why? Are you sending me?
[People say hello]
[In a charming tone]
Attorney Hong Cha-young
Come here.
[Exciting music]
(Myunghee)
Chayoung Hong
If you mess up just one more time, I'm Meg
I'm really dying, you bastard
If you get the chance, please kill me.
Have a near-death experience
[Chayoung’s laughter]
This is a really well-made dud, huh?
You don't strike out or anything like that.
One out, immediate kill
I'm sorry
[smiling slightly]
I need to cut my nails.
[In a charming tone]
Looks like it's slightly dented
[laughter]
[Chayoung laughs slightly]
(Myunghee)
Let's go, driver.
(people)
Come in!
Hey, really raise your hand, Mr.
[Disapproving groan]
[cell phone notification sound]
(Yoochan)
What is it? What again?
Wow
Why do you keep calling me, just, really
[dark music]
(Seokdo)
Now, even if you party today, don’t forget
(subordinates)
Yes, brother!
(Sunam)
Someone like the Italian ambassador
What if it comes again?
Okay, then let’s take them somewhere else.
(Seokdo)
Push it all!
(subordinates)
Yes, brother!
[Sunam answers]
[cell phone ringing sound]
(Sunam)
Hey, hey, get in!
[The subordinates are noisy]
Yes, team leader
Uh, tut.
Geumga Plaza for the next two months
[shaking breathing]
Just leave it alone
[Exciting music]
(Seokdo)
Oh, why?
If you want to leave it alone, leave it alone!
(Investment Development Team Leader)
When it gets smashed
We too are destroyed
- (Seokdo) Oh, what are you talking about, really?
- (Sunam) Hey, go!
(Seokdo)
Hey, don't go out, don't go out, ah, stay still
[Sunam continues to give orders]
Hey, hey, hey, stop!
Hey, wait, hey, stop!
Why is he stepping on Poclain like that? accelerator
No, stop!
Stop, no, stop!
[Sunam stops it]
Turn off the engine!
[Chuckling]
Turn off the engine, ah, fumes, mr.
[cell phone vibrating sound]
(Yoochan)
What if I disappear without saying a word?
Come home and have a glass of soju
[Meaningful music]
(Chayoung)
So, Babel Pharmaceutical’s narcotic painkiller
Turning people into drug addicts
There will also be drug cartels.
Let's stop it together?
Are you going to file lawsuits?
The lawsuit isn't important right now.
The key to this issue is drugs.
No, someone suddenly talked about drugs…
(Chayoung)
Maybe Vincenzo Cassano?
[sigh]
Now two minutes
I guess they also do ‘100 minute discussions’?
(Yoochan)
Because he’s an Italian lawyer
The seriousness of drugs and their organization
I know it better than anyone else
(Chayoung)
Other pharmaceutical companies
They make narcotic painkillers.
Why are you just holding a barbell and stretching?
Barbells are different
(Yoochan)
through the lobby
We will lower the level of hospital prescriptions.
It will produce quantities beyond imagination.
Almost like a fire extinguisher
Then, many people take that drug...
(Chayoung)
No matter how smart a person is
When reason becomes clouded
It's true that I'm obsessed with conspiracy theories.
Cha Young-ah
This is not a conspiracy theory, this is the truth and the future
[Doorbell rings]
I guess the debater is coming.
Have fun chatting
[Yoo-chan sighs]
[The door clicks open]
[The door slams shut]
[The gate slams shut]
Please tell my father
Let's not talk nonsense.
[Chayoung laughs]
Drugs? Big cartel?
What American drama do you write?
Is that so absurd?
Yes, just a little longer
I think Babel Pharmaceuticals will conquer the Earth too.
If you treat the truth with lies
The eyesight that sees the truth is
It makes you weak.
Now as a lawyer
Are you even denigrating my reputation?
[Vincenzo speaks in Italian]
[Laughs slightly]
Could you please add subtitles?
‘There is no honor among thieves’
[laughter]
[Interesting music]
someday you
I have the right to say these things
If it turns out that you don't exist
(Chayoung)
I will laugh at you every second of every day
So much so that you want to kill me
Let me say one more thing before it turns out.
[Italian]
Fool, fool!
[Chayoung chuckles]
[Korean]
Subtitles!
(Vincenzo)
There are no subtitles
[Chayoung’s angry groan]
Just hearing it makes me feel bad, huh?
At least it seems like an insult?
very annoying
Because I'm so pissed, it's catharsis
[laughter]
True
[Meaningful music]
(Chinese book)
It's all my fault
Yes, so that I don't become someone to you.
We will correct it as soon as possible, yes
No, no, yes
My brother is like this
Every time you scold me harshly
It seems like it's just growing, yeah
yes
Yes? A villa?
No, no
Yes, do whatever suits you, brother, yes.
Yes, brother, then again today
Goodbye, sleep well.
Yes, brother
[Puts down the glass]
[sigh]
What are we going to do, Mr.
[A dog barks in the distance]
[Yoo-chan’s refreshing groan]
(Vincenzo)
Lawyer
That woman
Did you say Mr. Oh Gyeong-ja?
Are you really okay?
It's not okay
There are only 6 months left
(Vincenzo)
um
If it rolls over, it will be very painful, right?
If you're that curious
[Pouring a drink]
To my mother earlier
I shouldn't have asked directly
[Calm music]
Next time I go see my mother
You can ask me directly.
How did you know?
I have been a lawyer for 30 years.
If you do it with a thud, it's fake.
(Yoochan)
Oh, and why did I ask the lawyer?
They must have forced me to take him to the hospital.
I really don't notice
Suddenly, I'm not a public defender?
When I brought it up
I already noticed it then.
In fact, it was from then
(Inspection)
Defendant Oh Kyeong-ja
During my life as a helper
My usual behavior is not good
From Chairman Hwang Deok-bae and his family
I have received frequent criticism
[Yoo-chan sighs]
On the day of the incident
Let's be pointed out about the defendant's insincerity.
I got angry and committed violence.
It led to death
[Vincenzo’s sigh]
(Attorney 3)
There is no difference
[Vincenzo’s sigh]
(Inspection)
Your Honor, the defendant, Oh Kyeong-ja,
One's own children in the past
I have thrown it away
[Vincenzo’s trembling breathing]
submitted by the defendant to an orphanage in Incheon.
Submit a waiver of parental rights
(Gyeongja)
What does that have to do with this?
(judge)
Defendant, be quiet.
[shaking breathing]
[Gyeongja sighs]
(Gyeongja)
Lawyer, please say something.
Rather, I was sexually assaulted.
[shaking breathing]
Chairman Hwang’s family
They're all lies
[Lawyer 3 speaks]
(Yoochan)
then
5 years ago at that time
I was so angry I didn’t know what to do
I saw a young man
That anger
I could feel it even from the seat next to me.
Like that in other people's business
Few people get angry
Unless it's family
[Picks up the bag]
[Sad music]
(Yoochan)
Oh, and a decisive blow
Are you sure you don’t want to go see your mother?
I won't force you
To forgive your mother
It's not going to be easy.
instead
Don't let longing become regret
[nervous music]
[Man 2’s heavy breathing]
[Gas hisses out]
[Button operation sound]
[Chuckling]
(Researcher 1)
What is this?
[People chuckle]
(Researcher 1)
Wow
[Gas hisses out]
(Researcher 2)
Wow, what is it?
[Notification rings]
[Meaningful music]
(Reporter on TV)
Around 3:30 this morning
At a villa in Yangyang, Gangwon-do
suspected to be a gas explosion
an accident occurred
Inside the villa at the time of the explosion
I was doing a project workshop
14 employees of Babel Pharmaceutical’s new drug development team
everyone died
No
[News continues]
This isn't really it!
[Yoo-chan’s angry breathing]
Lawyer
[sigh]
(Junwoo)
senior
The trial related to Babel Pharmaceuticals
Can’t I just take it?
Maraya, ask a senior to take charge of the trial?
People related to Babel Pharmaceuticals
Too many people have died
(Junwoo)
Well, it's not some kind of Death Note.
Oh, well, I'm afraid my senior might also make a mistake.
Why am I dying?
(Chayoung)
And I'm Babel Pharmaceuticals' litigator.
[Junwoo sighs]
(Junwoo)
No, people who died today
They are all Babel Pharmaceutical employees.
What does it matter?
Why are you so sensitive these days, huh?
(Chayoung)
suddenly emotionally
Are you getting anxious?
[English]
This is driving me crazy, listen to me
This is...
(Chayoung)
[Korean]
Get angry in Korean
(Junwoo)
Okay, okay, Korean, Korean, ah
Do people joke about worrying about other people?
What about your senior?
I have thoughts too
I’m doing this because it feels strange!
[sigh]
[lively music]
Intern Jang Jun-woo
Suddenly I feel it
(Chayoung)
Stay safe
And during work
I told you not to use English, right?
I'm filming American dramas alone
[sigh]
[Chayoung organizes the documents]
[Rumorizing documents]
[sigh]
[Chayoung hits the desk]
The briefing hasn't even started yet.
Today, I'm going to watch American dramas outside by myself.
I don’t speak Korean with my senior.
[English]
hello there
(Chayoung)
[Korean]
That guy, really
Hey! Intern Jang Jun-woo!
[English]
do you want to die
[Korean]
You're just doing it today!
[surprised elasticity]
(Seunghyuk)
No, this is
[Sighing]
Even though it was big, it was too big.
No, this is, ha
How…
Are you going to blow it all away?
Doesn’t this seem like a message?
(Myunghee)
‘Please, please work like this.
‘Make it hot’ or
'If you can't do it hotly,
'Nuge too, like Yadeul'
Oh, no way, what are you talking about…
(Seunghyuk)
Ah, well, another leap
They do it this badly, it's scary.
[Picks up a fork]
It's not a leap
Now Chairman Jang
I think they are giving us kusari.
[Myunghee puts down the plate]
Chairman Jang, that was his idea in the first place...
[cell phone vibrating sound]
This is Chairman Jang, Jang, Jang…
[nervous music]
[clears throat]
[Myunghee clears her throat]
Yes, Mr. Chairman.
Ah, preparations for fire compensation processing have begun.
(Seunghyuk)
Yes, yes?
Yes, yes, yes
Ah, yes
Then, meet with Attorney Choi Myung-hee until 12 o'clock.
I'll go in
Yes, sashimi…
[Call end sound]
I hung up…
Finally a meeting ceremony?
I guess I'll have to take it out soon.
What are you taking out?
(Myunghee)
uh
If you ask me anything, I'll teach you
My own magic bead
[laughter]
[In a charming tone]
Oh, what is it?
Sister, no, Choi, Attorney Choi
[The door clicks open]
My heart is pounding
[laughter]
[The door slams shut]
(Detective 1)
I'm on my way now
(Yoochan)
No, detailed investigation of the fire department.
There were no results either.
- (Yuchan) What kind of conclusion is completion?
- (Detective 2) Oh, that
(Detective 2)
In the first field investigation,
Most of the evidence came out
Through National Forensic Service forensics
There needs to be a thorough investigation into whether or not it was arson.
[Detective 2 sighs]
Arson was not found.
No more interfering with official duties.
What kind of obstruction is this?
(Detective 2)
I warned you
(Yoochan)
What a warning!
I'm talking about investigative principles.
(Detective 1)
Oh, this guy, stop it!
[Meaningful music]
- (Yoo-chan) Oh, let go of this, let go of this.
- (Detective 1) Yes?
(Vincenzo)
Don't touch me carelessly.
(Detective 1)
What are you?
(Yoochan)
If we don't conduct a detailed investigation,
I'm going to pitch a tent and live in front of here.
(Vincenzo)
Let's go out
- (Detective 1) Do whatever you want, then.
- (Yoochan) Let go of this.
(Vincenzo)
Let's go out
(Yoochan)
No, no
[The detectives are babbling]
IC
(Vincenzo)
Let's go
[Siren sounds]
[Vincenzo’s heavy breathing]
why take my advice
Are you not listening at all?
Are you saying we should get rid of Babel Pharmaceuticals?
At the scene where 14 people burned to death
Does that mean something like that?
[Vincenzo’s sigh]
What a lawyer can do now
All I can do is rage and mourn.
But that's not a lawyer's job.
To me, that's a lawyer's job too.
Without even fighting properly
I can't give in
If you don't give in
You have no choice but to pay a big price.
I know that better than anyone else.
If only Babel Pharmaceuticals could be punished.
I don't care if I die
[Yoo-chan’s urgent breathing]
(Vincenzo)
Why on earth are you so reckless?
Because that's my destiny
[Calm music]
(Yoochan)
A line on a playground tilted at 90 degrees
Even though I clearly know
Still, I will try to win
Running while struggling
Because it’s my job
What owns this world
Although they are smart people
Protecting this world is as reckless as mine.
These are people who are stuck
[Rough breathing]
[Interesting music]
Don't worry about the cost
Compensation for researchers who died at the villa
take care of it
yes, i understand
[Putting down the chopsticks]
Ah, my villa
(Chinese book)
That's really good material
It was built with a lot of effort.
no
Because of that one missing researcher
What is this!
Sorry, I'll do my best
(Seunghyuk)
Ah, the villa solution.
Thank you for scolding us.
What are you saying, what are you scolding me for?
I was just trying to relieve stress
[Awkward laughter]
No, that missing researcher.
Are you really not able to find it?
You'll find it in a few hours.
[Seunghyuk’s laughter]
(Seunghyuk)
To our lawyer Choi Myeong-hee
Well, there is a magic orb.
[Seunghyuk’s laughter]
Magic beads...
Magic, magic orb?
[Hanseo puts down his chopsticks]
There is such a thing
[laughter]
Our lawyer Choi
Because I made you come as an idol
Well, if you want anything, let me know.
I'll listen to everything
Then
Please buy the Southeastern District Prosecutor’s Office
[Interesting music]
[Refreshing moan]
What should I buy you? other…
- South, southeast? What is that?
- (Seunghyuk) Ah…
(Myunghee)
I'm talking about the Southeastern District Prosecutor's Office.
(Chinese book)
Ah…
How, how, what, can I buy it for you?
Where was the property for sale?
(Seunghyuk)
Yes?
[laugh]
We, ah, we
Our president is really fun, isn’t he?
[Seunghyuk’s laughter]
I heard the property is for sale? Southeastern District Prosecutors' Office
[Laughing]
What, does it come out as monthly rent? What about the charter?
[Atmospheric music plays]
(Myunghee)
Our CEO Han Seung-hyuk
The eyes that see people are young.
(Seunghyuk)
What is it again?
(Myunghee)
In Representative Han’s eyes, Jumma is
Bina as the head of Babel Group?
[laughter]
Oh, well, because I'm young and wild
we know
It's not the atmosphere of a group leader.
Poor understanding and unable to grasp the key points
Are you bluffing?
Oh, why, why, what again?
(Seunghyuk)
What's the problem?
Aida, there is such a thing.
(Seunghyuk)
[Laughing]
I'm so happy
[cell phone vibrating sound]
[nervous music]
(Myunghee)
Holy shit
What is it again?
It's a magic bead
I found the researcher who ran away.
[Seunghyuk’s laughter]
(Seunghyuk)
After all, our prosecutor, no, lawyer, no.
Hey, sister!
[Seunghyuk’s laughter]
(Myunghee)
Oh my!
But Uzzano?
Researcher and lawyer Hong Yu-chan
It was already happening
[nervous music]
Yes?
[cell phone vibrating sound]
Yes, Mr. Mincheol
(Mincheol)
I…
I will testify
[The sound of waves flows out]
(Mincheol)
Looking at my colleagues who died in the president's villa
I might suddenly become like that too.
I thought about it
So before that happens
I decided to reveal the truth
[Yoo-chan’s happy sigh]
(Yoochan)
Well thought out
Yes, I will do it tomorrow morning
I'll go pick you up.
yes
Yeah, see you tomorrow, yeah
[Welcome sigh]
(Student 3)
Hey, that's enough
(Youngho)
Almost legendary, this one
(Student 3)
yes
[Youngho’s laughter]
Hey, treat me as your brother.
(Youngho)
Oh, of course, have a drink.
[Student 3’s spirit]
[Youngho’s laughter]
- (Student 3) Oh, stay still!
- (Youngho) Oh, really
- (Student 3) Bring it, bring it
- (Youngho) Should I teach other kids too?
(Student 3)
Hey, we can't just do it on our own.
Of course I have to let you know
[Student 3 clicks his lighter]
Uh, no oil?
[Vincenzo stamps his foot]
[Interesting music]
(Vincenzo)
What am I doing here?
Why are you doing such useless things?
i
(Vincenzo)
yes
Let's not worry about anything else anymore
Finish it quickly
Let's leave
(Vincenzo)
Oh, I put out the fire in a hurry, but
Forced demolition by party
You can't keep stopping
(Yeonjin)
Yeah, yeah
(Cheolwook)
That's right
Now
Must stick
We have to bleed each other...
(Vincenzo)
Instead of seeing blood, I want to tell you
I'd like to give you a better suggestion.
[Vincenzo’s laughter]
[Cheolwook’s powerful moans]
The commercial building in the next neighborhood
I'm thinking of buying one
And you
I'm planning to move there.
(Yeonjin)
huh?
(Hongsik)
Hey, what does that mean?
Are you asking me to move?
without any conditions
I'm giving you a shopping mall.
- (Yeonjin) Oh, for free?
- (Hongsik) Huh?
[Interesting music]
- (Vincenzo) Yes
- (Heesu) No, does that make sense?
(Heesu)
Why are you giving it to us for free?
Because that's the best way
Wait a minute
(Larry Kang)
There is a saying in the West like this:
‘Free cheese is only found in mousetraps’
(Heesu)
That's what I heard and saw
Free is dangerous
No, it's not dangerous at all.
(Vincenzo)
When you purchase a building, you
Just move it
Oh, so we just have to go with our bodies?
(Kiseok)
Oh, awesome
(in advance)
But who is you...
(Yeonjin)
So, who are you?
(Toto)
Oh yes, my student, yes
Your respect for me is just very strong
A disciple who likes his food
[People's elasticity]
(Kiseok)
Nice to meet you
(Hongsik)
Uh, draw it
Child, in its own way
Because it seems like our lawyer’s sincerity.
(in advance)
Let's believe it, right?
[in a low voice]
No, how much have we seen?
Do you know the truth?
(in advance)
[smiling slightly]
I think I know
(Hongsik)
Well, if you think about it,
[Yeonjin responds]
What did the lawyer tell us?
They said there was something I had to leave out.
- (Yeonjin) None.
- (Hongsik) Yes
(Larry Kang)
No, even if I know ten ways underwater
We, the people of one path, do not know what is inside...
- (In advance) Director Larry
- (Larry Kang) Yes?
Because I don’t have eyes to see people like this
It's different for women.
[People laughing]
[Larry Kang laughs]
(Larry Kang)
Wow, me
Have you never been kicked?
[Crying]
I've never been in a relationship, so I don't have one.
[Larry Kang laughs]
(Chae Shin)
Okay, everyone.
[moktak sound effect]
Faithfulness and faith are the mother of merit, and
It is said to be the road to Buddha.
We all take this opportunity
merit of faith
How about stacking it up?
[elegant music]
[People respond]
Thank you, monk.
Okay, everyone.
Then everyone agrees with me
I assume you agree.
[Exciting music plays]
One, two, one, two
[A knocking sound is heard]
Did you come in?
[Myunghee hums]
Did you call me?
(Myunghee)
Uh, one, two, sit down.
[TV power sound]
Let's see, now, now
[Myunghee’s refreshing groan]
As of today
In the Babel Group-related complaint case
hands off
[Exciting music]
I won't accept it
Oh, it's not my order, it's the representative's order.
Still I won't accept it
Well, there is all this, right?
(Myunghee)
[screaming]
Are you the CEO of this company? Tsk
It's a unilateral order with little basis.
can't hear
Why is there no basis?
He said he would look after my father.
You're not doing your job properly!
I've never been like that
Not as a father, but as an opposing lawyer...
[Myunghee laughs]
(Myunghee)
That's what you say, right?
business
You can't crush heavenly principles, right?
Even though I can't win in one shot
go out
Yes, really.
[Laughing]
Now there is new hope
yes
just trust me
[Yuchan’s laughter]
(Yoochan)
yes
[Yuchan’s laughter]
Ah
(Joosung)
I don't know what's going on
But you suddenly got promoted.
[Yuchan’s laughter]
Suddenly?
(Yoochan)
Yes, ah, I'll be there tomorrow evening
I'll get back to you
yes, yes
Uh, lawyer, what about lunch?
(Vincenzo)
No, well, not yet.
- (Yoochan) Hey, what should I order?
- (Joosung) Oh, is that so?
(Yoochan)
Hey, hey, it's been a while since I've had sweet and sour pork
[clicks tongue]
- How are you?
- (Joosung) Are you serious?
- (Yoochan) Oh
- (Joosung) Oh, the first, the first.
[Yuchan’s laughter]
(Joosung)
I'm awesome...
[sigh]
Please talk to me, Attorney Hong Yoo-chan.
(Joosung)
Because I said ‘Attorney Hong Yu-chan’
One Jindo dog, emergency evacuation
[English]
Nucleus detected
[Interesting music]
(Chayoung)
[Korean]
I understand if you don't help me with my work.
Then at least my future path is
It's not something you should stop.
(Yoochan)
Why am I blocking your path?
(Chayoung)
Thanks to my father, the company
It looks like it's being pushed back a lot.
The popular super car became a shit car.
(Yoochan)
Well, because I went into the shithole.
It becomes a shit car.
(Chayoung)
Oh, someone with a conscience
Why don't you acknowledge the differences in values?
(Yoochan)
This is not a matter of difference
It's a matter of right and wrong
[Vincenzo’s groans in pain]
[nervous music]
[takes a breath]
[angry moaning]
But every time
I'm going to scratch my dad again today.
The person who lived such a righteous life
(Chayoung)
Are you letting your mom go like that?
[Calm music]
You care about other people
Are you letting my mom die alone in the operating room?
I told you to stop talking about that.
(Chayoung)
No, I'll do it forever
My father took my mother and me
It made me unhappy.
(Yoochan)
Get out!
[Calm music plays]
[Chayoung laughs]
[Vincenzo’s groans in pain]
(Chayoung)
When I talk about my mom
[Calm music]
Did you get stabbed?
other people
Taking the lead like that
Why did you neglect your mother?
Because I don't want to hear it
get out
(Chayoung)
my father
hundreds, thousands of people
Even if you save the wronged person
The punishment for sending my mom like that
You will never escape
[Vincenzo is rumbling]
[Calm music plays]
[The door slams shut]
Ha, sorry
Oh, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay
(Yoochan)
Oh, sorry.
Because it looks ugly between father and daughter
[Calm music]
(Vincenzo)
[in pain]
I-I'm sorry.
(Yoochan)
It's okay, it's okay
[Moaning in pain]
[Refreshing moan]
Oh, really
How can you not say a word that you were wrong?
[sigh]
[It’s raining heavily]
[The door bell rings]
[The door slams shut]
[Chayoung rattles the can]
[Chayoung sighs]
[The door bell rings]
Why?
Couldn't you have said it more maturely?
yes?
(Vincenzo)
I'm not the best lawyer.
I felt like a spoiled high school girl
Like the pictures in the lawyer's house
No, cowardly
You're bringing up someone else's dark history!
Arrows shot by children at their parents
Without exception, I regret every single step.
[Soft music]
(Vincenzo)
Don't do anything you'll regret
Regret is experienced in reality
Because it is the biggest hell
I'm going to have a drink at my father's favorite bar.
Come if you have any thoughts
You don't need to apologize
Let's just sit together
(Chayoung)
Ha, indeed
Apple?
sounds like an apple
[Soft music plays]
[Thunder rumbles]
[nervous music]
[Call connection tone]
[Thunder rumbles]
Yes, beads
start working
[Thunder rumbles]
no
both
[Thunder rumbles]
[Yoo-chan sighs]
(Yoochan)
Even if I hold on well
Times like this are the hardest.
These damn children
If you harm my daughter
No matter what I say
Our Chayoung
What a precious daughter, they, mr.
[Yoo-chan sighs]
(Vincenzo)
We will get through this well.
Attorney Hong Cha-young is a strong person.
You are a lawyer
Aren't you really a strong person?
[Vincenzo pours a drink]
[Makes mouth sound]
Even someone that strong
not a good person
People who are fundamentally evil
He won't come to his mother's trial for abandoning him.
How is my mother so unhappy?
I just went to check.
[Calm music]
Are you serious?
yes
Even the lawyer
Lawyer Hong takes care of his father's misfortune.
don't make me check
I'm saying don't fight with the Babel Group.
Because I would be unhappy?
I
I will keep fighting
I have new motivation to fight
That power is
(Vincenzo)
And the lawyer
It's dangerous, right?
[Vincenzo puts down his chopsticks]
The former lawyer
I don't like taking risks alone.
Just this time
I hope you become a coward
To me, cowardice means
Not running away
You're putting other people at risk.
(Yoochan)
Yes?
[Yoo-chan puts down his glass]
[Yoo-chan’s refreshing groan]
[sigh]
(Chayoung)
Chi
I'm not going to see my father
Tofu and kimchi at Silbi’s house in Namdo
I'm going to eat assorted pancakes.
[The door opens and closes with a click]
[The door bell rings]
(employee)
me, customer
This
What is it?
(employee)
The man who spoke with the customer earlier
Give it to me when you go.
[Calm music]
[The door opens and closes with a click]
[The door bell rings]
What is it
Tsk
[pleasant breathing sound]
[nervous music]
[Mincheol blinks]
“Babel Pharmaceutical”
[A knocking sound is heard]
Who are you?
who are you?
(Hyeokpil)
It's the police
What's going on?
(Hyeokpil)
Checking in progress
A robbery and murder suspect appears nearby.
Just take a moment to verify your identity.
Please cooperate
Could you please open the door?
Busan police speak Seoul language?
Yes, I'm from Seoul
Oh yes, just wait a moment.
[Music that heightens tension]
(Hyeokpil)
Please open it quickly, I'm a bit busy too.
(Mincheol)
Yeah, just a moment.
[The door is pounding]
[Mincheol’s urgent breathing]
[The lock falls off]
[Mincheol falls down]
(Hyeokpil)
IC
[Mincheol’s moans of pain]
[Mincheol’s heavy breathing]
[Rough breathing]
[Mincheol’s urgent breathing]
(Yoochan)
I am
Jackie Chan, Jackie Chan
This guy's movie is so funny
Why? Jackie Chan
Pukpukpuk, because I’m good at fighting
It's not about winning.
You win because you never give up.
Even if I get NG 10 or 100 times
Tap, tap, tap until you hear the OK!
[laughter]
Uh, I woke up and smoked a cigarette.
Puk puk!
[Yuchan’s laughter]
(Yoochan)
Oh, why is it raining so much...
[cell phone vibrating sound]
[nervous music]
[Dark sound effect]
[sigh]
[Drunk moaning]
(Hwang Gyu)
Me, sir, just one cigarette.
Can I borrow it?
(Yoochan)
Oh, yes, that's right.
Well here it is
Yes, ah, fire?
[Yoo-chan lights the lighter]
[Yuchan laughs slightly]
[Meaningful sound effects]
Have a nice smoke
(Hwang Gyu)
yes, thank you
[Thunder rumbles]
[cell phone vibrating sound]
[Calm music]
[sigh]
[Mincheol’s trembling breathing]
[Call connection tone]
[shaking breathing]
[Guidance voice]
You will receive a call now...
[Call connection tone]
[Mincheol’s trembling breathing]
[A knocking sound is heard]
[Music that heightens tension]
[Mincheol’s heavy breathing]
[Frightened groan]
[Mincheol is very happy]
(Yoochan)
Oh my
[Thunder rumbles]
It's raining a lot, huh?
[Calm music]
[Yoo-chan sighs]
Lawyer, by any chance
[Pours a drink]
Are you hiding something from me?
There is
My true heart no one knows
[Speaks Italian]
(Yoochan)
‘The devil drives out the devil’
[laughter]
The only thing I memorize
It's an Italian proverb.
I told you this before, right?
A monster can fight a monster
But I can't be a monster
Someone really showed up as a monster
It's the law and damn it
These bad guys just
I wish it were all swept away
[laughter]
But well, reality is impossible.
[Makes mouth sound]
Attorney Vincenzo
You can't be that monster, right?
[Laughs]
[Yoo-chan clears his throat]
(Vincenzo)
There was an urgent phone call earlier.
I thought it was coming?
yes? Urgent call?
(Vincenzo)
RDU
RDU-90
Isn't that the researcher?
[Embarrassed groan]
[Mobile phone operation sound]
[Call connection tone]
[Sharp sound effect]
[Meaningful music]
[Thunder rumbles]
[Music that heightens the mood]
Subtitle: Kwon Jeong-won